Usage: next dev [directory] [options]

Starts Next.js in development mode with hot-code reloading, error reporting,
and more.

Arguments:
  [directory]                              A directory on which to build the application. If no directory is provided, the current directory will be used.

Options:
  --turbo                                  Starts development mode using Turbopack.
  --turbopack                              Starts development mode using Turbopack.
  -p, --port <port>                        Specify a port number on which to start the application. (default: 3000, env: PORT)
  -H, --hostname <hostname>                Specify a hostname on which to start the application (default: 0.0.0.0).
  --disable-source-maps                    Don't start the Dev server with `--enable-source-maps`. (default: false)
  --experimental-https                     Starts the server with HTTPS and generates a self-signed certificate.
  --experimental-https-key, <path>         Path to a HTTPS key file.
  --experimental-https-cert, <path>        Path to a HTTPS certificate file.
  --experimental-https-ca, <path>          Path to a HTTPS certificate authority file.
  --experimental-upload-trace, <traceUrl>  Reports a subset of the debugging trace to a remote HTTP URL. Includes sensitive data.
  -h, --help                               Displays this message.
